# **BRADLEY MAUNCHO**

Nairobi, Kenya | bmauncho@gmail.com | + 254 706 118 458 | LinkedIn | E-Portfolio

#### **CAREER PROFILE**

A game developer with a background in digital art and interactive media design. Using my 6+ years of skills and experience, I apply myself to projects for individuals and companies that require ideation, research, and game development using Unity and Blender as the mediums of choice.

## CAREER ACHIEVEMENTS

- Ideated and developed the Hawker 101 exhibited in Documetor 15-Kassel Germany (an international program
  for creatives and global game developers) as the only Kenyan RPG
   Game
- **Developed 4+ games** from conceptualization to final drafts in the less than 1 year **Developed a VR modern space** in 3 months.

### **TOOLS & SOFTWARE**

• **Software Skills**: Unity, Blender, 3DS Max, Maya, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe After Effects, Adobe Illustrator,

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MEKAN GAMES

Nairobi, Kenya

2022-Present

- Developed and tested various mobile game concepts on the market.
  - Ideation of various hyper casual game concepts to compete with existing concepts.
  - Designed and developed game mechanics and levels for a concept game that was being tested in the market.
  - Collaborated with a team of artists and designers to create and implement game assets, resulting in a 30% improvement in overall game aesthetics and user experience.
  - Optimized game performance and memory usage, reducing load times by 40% and improving overall game stability by 50%.

CABA HABILIMENTS CANADA (REMOTE)
Lead Video Animator | storyboarding FEB 2022 -APRIL 2022

- Created a storyboard as a visualization of the solution.
- Visualized an ad for CADA Habiliments which was displayed on "The Black Authority "YouTube channel.
- Optimized the animation process by creating the assets required.

MOOV CAFE& BISTRO

NAIROBI, KENYA

Video Animator | Visual Designer

DEC 2021 - APRIL 2022

• Improved the online performance of the cafe by creating visually appealing designs and posters.

- Created an ad that was utilized to establish a user-centered interaction with the cafe's clients and potential clients.
- Developed over 20+ design projects.
- Frequently integrated photographic, graphic, and typographic elements into the designs.

# GAMARA DESIGN Co-founder | Lead Game Developer | Animator | Illustrator | Graphic Designer 2019-2022

- Enhanced the company's online performance by generating aesthetically appealing graphics and ads.
- Used Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, and Adobe After Effects in my daily designs.
- Led two designers to develop products and graphic materials.
- Boosted client transactions by an average of 25%.
- Led team project meetings to drive toward increasing e-commerce client revenue. Frequently integrated photographic, graphic, and typographic elements.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **GROWTH**

# THE KENYA TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY Bachelor of TECHNOLOGY( DESIGN)

Nairobi, Kenya 2018

- Coursework: User-centered design, Game Development, Animation, Web& App Development
- Project work; User-centered design, Game Development

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: Animating, storyboarding, Scripting languages (i.e., C#, JavaScript, cascading style sheets), User experience (UX) design, User interface (UI) design, digital art, game design, game development, Game mechanics, level design, version control systems (e.g., Git) and Game engine proficiency (e.g., Unity).
- **Certifications:** Animation techniques with 3D effects in After Effects from Domestika, Game Development (First-person Shooter with c#,) and (First-person Shooter with c# )from Udemy.

# REFERENCES

# • Flora Mutere,

Tutor, The Technical University of Kenya.

Nairobi, Kenya

Phone: +254 716 552723 flora.mutere@tukenya.ac.ke

## • Kianga Emman,

Tutor, The Technical University of Kenya.

Nairobi, Kenya

Phone: +254 706 759075

emman.kianga@tukenya.ac.ke